Harvard College Observatory observations, logs, instrument readings, and calculations: an inventory
Harvard College Observatory observations, logs, instrument readings, and calculations
- [Positions of Nebulae], vol. 6, 1909-02-01 to 1909-04-01; KG11367.015 (Box 262)
- [Positions of Nebulae], vol. 7, 1909-04-01 to 1909-08-01; KG11367.016 (Box 262)
  Also identified as: G9.
- [Positions of Nebulae], vol. 8, 1909-06-01 to 1909-09-01; KG11367.017 (Box 262)
  Also identified as: G10.
- [Positions of Nebulae], vol. 9, 1909-09-01 to 1909-10-01; KG11367.018 (Box 262)
  Also identified as: G11.
- [Positions of Nebulae], vol. 10, 1909-11-01 to 1910-08-01; KG11367.019 (Box 263)
  Also identified as: G12.
- [Positions of Nebulae], vol. 11, 1910-08-01 to 1910-09-01; KG11367.020 (Box 263)
  Also identified as: G13.
- [Positions of Nebulae] marked by Dr. Shalley, 1., KG11367.021 (Box 263)
  Also identified as: G14.
- [Positions of Nebulae] marked by Dr. Shalley, 2., 1923-07-01 to 1923-08-01; KG11367.022 (Box 263)
  Also identified as: G15.
- [Positions of Nebulae] discovered by D. Menzel, 1., 1922-07-01 to 1922-08-01; KG11367.023 (Box 263)
  Also identified as: G16.
  Donald Menzel.
- [Positions of Nebulae] discovered by D. Menzel, 2., 1922-08-01; KG11367.024 (Box 263)
  Also identified as: G17.
- [Positions of Nebulae] discovered by D. Menzel, 3., 1922-08-01; KG11367.025 (Box 263)
  Also identified as: G18.
- [Positions of Nebulae] discovered by D. Menzel, 4., 1922-08-01; KG11367.026 (Box 263)
  Also identified as: G19.
- [Positions of Nebulae] Coma-Virgo, 1., 1927-02-01 to 1927-03-01; KG11367.027 (Box 263)
  Also identified as: G20.
  Adelaide Ames.
- [Positions of Nebulae] Coma-Virgo, 2., 1927; KG11367.028 (Box 263)
  Also identified as: G21.
- [Positions of Nebulae] Coma-Virgo, 3., 1927; KG11367.029 (Box 263)
  Also identified as: G22.
- [Positions of Nebulae] Coma-Virgo, 4., KG11367.030 (Box 263)
  Also identified as: G23.
- [Positions of Nebulae] Coma-Virgo, 5., KG11367.031 (Box 263)
  Also identified as: G24.
- [Diameter, Circumference] Coma-Virgo, 6., KG11367.032 (Box 263)
  Also identified as: G25.
- Positions, magnitudes, diameters [Coma-Virgo], 7., KG11367.033 (Box 263)
  Also identified as: G26.
- Positions, magnitudes, diameters [Coma-Virgo], 8., KG11367.034 (Box 263)
  Also identified as: G27.
- Positions, magnitudes, diameters, S. Gal. Pole, 9., KG11367.035 (Box 263)
  Also identified as: G28.
- Positions, magnitudes, diameters Coma-Virgo, -30° to -60°, 10., KG11367.036 (Box 264)
  Also identified as: G29.
- Identifications and Magnitudes of NGC Objects, 11., KG11367.037 (Box 264)
  Also identified as: G30.
- Identifications and Magnitudes, Coma-Vir. ext., 12., KG11367.038 (Box 264)
  Also identified as: G31.
- Plate counts Coma-Vir ext., 13, KG11367.039 (Box 264)
  Also identified as: G32.
  Adelaide Ames and R.W. Ford.
- Positions of new neb. on A plates, 1., KG11367.040 (Box 264)
  Also identified as: G33.
  C.D. Boyd.
- Positions of nebulae, 2., KG11367.041 (Box 264)
  Also identified as: G34.
  Sylvia F. Mussels.
- Positions of nebulae, 3., KG11367.042 (Box 264)
  Also identified as: G35.
  Muriel E. Mussels Seyfert.
- Positions of nebulae, 4., KG11367.043 (Box 264)
  Also identified as: G36.
- Positions of nebulae, 5., KG11367.044 (Box 264)
  Also identified as: G37.
- Positions of nebulae, 6., KG11367.045 (Box 264)
  Also identified as: G38.
- Positions of nebulae, 7., KG11367.046 (Box 264)
  Also identified as: G39.
- Positions of nebulae, 8., KG11367.047 (Box 264)
  Also identified as: G40.
- Positions of nebulae, 9., KG11367.048 (Box 264)
  Also identified as: G41.
- Positions of nebulae, 10., KG11367.049 (Box 264)
  Also identified as: G42.
  Muriel E. Mussels Seyfert and Sylvia F. Mussels.
- Positions of nebulae, 11., KG11367.050 (Box 264)
  Also identified as: G43.
- Positions of nebulae, 12., KG11367.051 (Box 264)
  Also identified as: G44.
- Positions of nebulae, 13., KG11367.052 (Box 264)
  Also identified as: G45.
- Positions of nebulae, 14., KG11367.053 (Box 264)
  Also identified as: G46.
- Summary of Work Accomplished, A., KG11367.054 (Box 264)
  Also identified as: G47.
- Classifications and Diameters, B., KG11367.055 (Box 265)
  Also identified as: G48.
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, C., KG11367.056 (Box 265)
  Also identified as: G49.
- Classifications and Diameters, D., KG11367.057 (Box 265)
  Also identified as: G50.
- Classifications and Diameters, E., KG11367.058 (Box 265)
  Also identified as: G51.
- Nebula counter per sq. degree, F., KG11367.059 (Box 265)
  Also identified as: G52.
- Magnitudes of clusters of nebulae, G., KG11367.060 (Box 265)
  Also identified as: G53.
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, H., KG11367.061 (Box 265)
  Also identified as: G54.
- Diameter of brightest nebulae, J., KG11367.062 (Box 265)
  Also identified as: G55.
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, K., KG11367.063 (Box 265)
  Also identified as: G56.
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, L., KG11367.064 (Box 265)
  Also identified as: G57.
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, M., KG11367.065 (Box 265)
  Also identified as: G58.
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, N., KG11367.066 (Box 265)
  Also identified as: G59.
- Classifications of Nebulae, O., KG11367.067 (Box 265)
  Also identified as: G60.
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, P., KG11367.068 (Box 265)
  Also identified as: G61.
- Classifications and Diameters of Nebulae, Q., KG11367.069 (Box 265)
  Also identified as: G62.
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, R., KG11367.070 (Box 265)
  Also identified as: G63.
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, S., KG11367.071 (Box 265)
  Also identified as: G64.
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, T., KG11367.072 (Box 265)
  Also identified as: G65.
- Classifications of Nebulae, U., KG11367.073 (Box 265)
  Also identified as: G66.
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, V., KG11367.074 (Box 265)
  Also identified as: G67.
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, W., KG11367.075 (Box 266)
  Also identified as: G68.
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, X., KG11367.076 (Box 266)
  Also identified as: G69.
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, Y., KG11367.077 (Box 266)
  Also identified as: G70.
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, Z., KG11367.078 (Box 266)
  Also identified as: G71.
- Examination of A Plates, A'., 1936 to 1939; KG11367.079 (Box 266)
  Also identified as: G72.
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, B'., KG11367.080 (Box 266)
  Also identified as: G73.
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, C'., KG11367.081 (Box 266)
  Also identified as: G74.
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, D'., KG11367.082 (Box 266)
  Also identified as: G75.
  Muriel E. Mussels Seyfert and C.D. Boyd.
- Revised Nebula Counts, F'., KG11367.083 (Box 266)
  Also identified as: G76.
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, G'., KG11367.084 (Box 266)
  Also identified as: G77.
  C.D. Boyd and F.W. Wright.
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, H'., KG11367.085 (Box 266)
  Also identified as: G78.
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, I'., KG11367.086 (Box 266)
  Also identified as: G79.
- Positions of Nebulae, J'., KG11367.087 (Box 266)
  Also identified as: G80.
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, K'., KG11367.088 (Box 266)
  Also identified as: G81.
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, L'., KG11367.089 (Box 266)
  Also identified as: G82.
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, M'., KG11367.090 (Box 266)
  Also identified as: G83.
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, N'., KG11367.091 (Box 266)
  Also identified as: G84.
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, O'., KG11367.092 (Box 266)
  Also identified as: G85.
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, P'., KG11367.093 (Box 266)
  Also identified as: G86.
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, Q'., KG11367.094 (Box 266)
  Also identified as: G87.
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, R'., KG11367.095 (Box 266)
  Also identified as: G88.
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, S'., KG11367.096 (Box 266)
  Also identified as: G89.
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, T'., KG11367.097 (Box 266)
  Also identified as: G90.
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, U'., KG11367.098 (Box 266)
  Also identified as: G91.
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, V'., KG11367.099 (Box 266)
  Also identified as: G92.
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, W'., KG11367.100 (Box 267)
  Also identified as: G93.
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, X'., KG11367.101 (Box 267)
  Also identified as: G94.
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, Y'., KG11367.102 (Box 267)
  Also identified as: G95.
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, Z'., KG11367.103 (Box 267)
  Also identified as: G96.
  F.W. Wright.
- Examination of Nebulae, KG11367.104 (Box 267)
  Also identified as: G97.
- Coma-Virgo Ext. Magnitudes, vol. 1, 1935; KG11367.105 (Box 267)
  Also identified as: G101.
  J. Cuffey.
- Coma-Virgo Ext. Magnitudes, vol. 2, 1935; KG11367.106 (Box 267)
  Also identified as: G102.
- Nebular Counts, 1935 to 1937; KG11367.107 (Box 267)
  Also identified as: G103.
  B. Lindsay.
- Positions of Nebulae, KG11367.108 (Box 267)
  Also identified as: G104.
- Magnitudes of Faint Nebulae, KG11367.109 (Box 267)
  Also identified as: G105.
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, 1935 to 1937; KG11367.110 (Box 267)
  Also identified as: G106.
- N.G. Cao Magnitudes, KG11367.111 (Box 267)
  Also identified as: G107.
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, KG11367.112 (Box 267)
  Also identified as: G108.
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, KG11367.113 (Box 267)
  Also identified as: G109.
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, KG11367.114 (Box 267)
  Also identified as: G110.
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, KG11367.115 (Box 267)
  Also identified as: G111.
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, KG11367.116 (Box 267)
  Also identified as: G112.
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, KG11367.117 (Box 267)
  Also identified as: G113.
- Magnitudes, Diameters of Nebulae, KG11367.118 (Box 267)
  Also identified as: G114.
  R.L. Paraboschi.
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, KG11367.119 (Box 267)
  Also identified as: G115.
- Magnitude on Overlapping Plates, KG11367.120 (Box 267)
  Also identified as: G116.
- 15th Magnitude Survey, M1, KG11367.121 (Box 267)
  Also identified as: G117.
- 16th Magnitude Survey, M2, KG11367.122 (Box 267)
  Also identified as: G118.
- 17th Magnitude Survey, 1935; KG11367.123 (Box 268)
  Also identified as: G119.
  N.J. Oliver.
- Classifications and Diameters, KG11367.124 (Box 268)
  Also identified as: G125.
  C.K. Seyfert.
- Classifications and Diameters, KG11367.125 (Box 268)
  Also identified as: G126.
- Positions, 1., KG11367.126 (Box 268)
  Also identified as: G127.
- Magnitudes, KG11367.127 (Box 268)
  Also identified as: G128.
- Magnitudes, KG11367.128 (Box 268)
  Also identified as: G129.
- MC Records of Nebulae, summary, KG11367.129 (Box 268)
  Also identified as: G130.
- MC Magnitude of Nebulae, KG11367.130 (Box 268)
  Also identified as: G131.
- MC Classification and Diameters, KG11367.131 (Box 268)
  Also identified as: G132.
- MC Nebulae count, KG11367.132 (Box 268)
  Also identified as: G133.
- MC North Polar Cap: Positions, KG11367.133 (Box 268)
  Also identified as: G134.
- MC Plate counters, KG11367.134 (Box 268)
  Also identified as: G135.
- MC North Polar Cap: Magnitudes, KG11367.135 (Box 268)
  Also identified as: G136.
  P.B.J..
  P.B.J. identity uncertain.
- MC North Polar Cap: Magnitudes, KG11367.136 (Box 268)
  Also identified as: G137.
- MC Magnitudes, VII, KG11367.137 (Box 268)
  Also identified as: G138.
- MC Magnitudes, VIII, KG11367.138 (Box 268)
  Also identified as: G139.
- MC Magnitudes, IX, KG11367.139 (Box 268)
  Also identified as: G140.
- MC Magnitudes, X, KG11367.140 (Box 268)
  Also identified as: G141.
- MC Magnitudes, XI, KG11367.141 (Box 268)
  Also identified as: G142.
- MC Magnitudes, XII, KG11367.142 (Box 268)
  Also identified as: G143.
- MC Magnitudes, XIII, KG11367.143 (Box 268)
  Also identified as: G144.
- MC Magnitudes, XIV, KG11367.144 (Box 268)
  Also identified as: G145.
- MC Magnitudes, XV, KG11367.145 (Box 268)
  Also identified as: G146.
- Variables in SMC, LMC, 1., 1935 to 1939; KG11367.146 (Box 269)
  Virginia McKibben Nail and F.W. Wright, R.K. Marshall.
- Variables in SMC, LMC, 2., KG11367.147 (Box 269)
  Virginia McKibben Nail and R.A. Craig.
- Variables in SMC, LMC, 3., KG11367.148 (Box 269)
  Virginia McKibben Nail and A.F. Swan.
- [Variables] in Vela-Carina, 4., KG11367.149 (Box 269)
- [Variables] in SMC, 5., 1945; KG11367.150 (Box 269)
  A.S. Carlston.
- [Variables] in SMC, 6a., KG11367.151 (Box 269)
  Virginia McKibben Nail and F.W. Wright.
- [Variables] in LMC, SMC, 6b., 1941 to 1951; KG11367.152 (Box 269)
  Virginia McKibben Nail and F.W. Wright, A. Hearn, M.D. Ashbrook.
- [Variables] in LMC, SMC, 8., KG11367.153 (Box 269)
  Virginia McKibben Nail and Virginia McKibben Nail, F.W. Wright.
- [Variables] in SMC, 9., KG11367.154 (Box 269)
  R.K. Marshall and E.M. Cork.
- [Variables] in SMC, 10., KG11367.155 (Box 269)
  Virginia McKibben Nail.
- Variables in SMC, 30 Dor (?), 11., KG11367.156 (Box 269)
  Virginia McKibben Nail and M.R. Hunt.
- [Variables] 47 Tuc., 12., KG11367.157 (Box 269)
- [Variables] LMC, SMC, 13., KG11367.158 (Box 269)
  Virginia McKibben Nail and M.S. Matthews.
- [Variables], 14., KG11367.159 (Box 269)
- [Variables] SMC, 47 Tuc, NGC362, 15., KG11367.160 (Box 269)
- [Variables] SMC, LMC, 17., KG11367.161 (Box 269)
- [Variables] SMC, 18., 1932; KG11367.162 (Box 269)
  M.B. Leavens.
- MWF 182, MWF 188, SMC, LMC, 19., KG11367.163 (Box 269)
  Mildred B. Shapley and Virginia McKibben Nail.
- M55, LMC Variable, 28., 1934; KG11367.164 (Box 269)
  Jenka Mohr and Virginia McKibben Nail.
- Variables in LMC, 30., 1954 to 1955; KG11367.165 (Box 269)
- Variables in LMC, 31., 1952; KG11367.166 (Box 269)
  B. Lindsay and Virginia McKibben Nail.
- Variables in LMC, 32., KG11367.167 (Box 269)
  M. Ryder.
- Variables in LMC, 33., KG11367.168 (Box 269)
- Variables in LMC, SMC, 34., 1950 to 1954; KG11367.169 (Box 269)
  William G. Tifft and J. Swartzmann.
- Variables in LMC (HA 90 #1), 35., KG11367.170 (Box 270)
  Henrietta S. Leavitt and Sylvia F. Mussels.
- Variables LMC, 1., KG11367.171 (Box 270)
  Also labeld as FWW1.
- Variables SMC, 2., KG11367.172 (Box 270)
  Also labeld as FWW2.
- Variables SMC, 3., KG11367.173 (Box 270)
  Also labeld as FWW3.
- Red Variables, 4., KG11367.174 (Box 270)
  Also labeld as FWW4.
- Variables in NGC1846, 2315, 5., KG11367.175 (Box 270)
  Also labeld as FWW5.
- Variables in omega Cen, NGC4833, NGC7099, Var. 1, KG11367.176 (Box 270)
  Also labeld as FWW Var. 1.
- Variables in NGC 3201, Var. 2, KG11367.177 (Box 270)
  Also labeld as FWW Var. 2.
- Variables in NGC 3201, Var. 3, KG11367.178 (Box 270)
  Also labeld as FWW Var. 3.
- Milky Way Bureau, Red Maps, Book 3., KG11367.179 (Box 270)
  Also labeld as FWW Bk.III.
- Leo I - periods; Vela, KG11367.180 (Box 270)
  Also labeld as FWW.
- Variables in omega Cen, 11., KG11367.181 (Box 270)
  Book in poor condition.
- Variables in omega Cen, 12., KG11367.182 (Box 270)
- Variables in omega Cen, 13., KG11367.183 (Box 270)
- Variables in omega Cen.; miscellaneous variables, 17., KG11367.184 (Box 270)
- K. Crucis, KG11367.185 (Box 270)
- Hercules Cluster, KG11367.186 (Box 270)
- Messier 5, 2., KG11367.187 (Box 270)
- Omega Centauri; Eros 2., KG11367.188 (Box 270)
- Measurments of Clusters, no. 1., KG11367.189 (Box 270)
  E.H. identity uncertain; Book in poor condition..
- Discussion of Measures of Clusters, no. 2., KG11367.190 (Box 270)
- Measures of Clusters, no 3., KG11367.191 (Box 271)
- Measures of Clusters in Per.; Observations and Magnitudes, 43., 1903; KG11367.192 (Box 271)
- Work on Magnitude Clouds, 1924 to 1925; KG11367.193 (Box 271)
  H.H. Wilson.
- Variables in Agl and Sct -- mostly NA plates, 1931 to 1937; KG11367.194 (Box 271)
  R.M. Hindiman and E.F. Sanborn.
- Shorthand notes, 1921 to 1926; KG11367.195 (Box 271)
  Harlow Shapley.
- Cluster in Perseus, Positions and Magnitudes, 42., 1903; KG11367.196 (Box 271)
- Variables in LMC, 1931; KG11367.197 (Box 271)
- Miscellaneous; Variables, 53., KG11367.198 (Box 271)
- Variables in Car. and Vel., Z., KG11367.199 (Box 271)
- Measurements at Maria Mitchell, KG11367.200 (Box 271)
- Work on Spectra, 1921; KG11367.201 (Box 271)
- Miscellaneous Variable Star Work, 15., 1921 to 1946; KG11367.202 (Box 271)
  Arville Walker.
- Tests on 60-inch telescope, 1924 to 1926; KG11367.203 (Box 271)
- LMC variables - magnitudes, 1931; KG11367.204 (Box 271)
  Natalie Ross.
- Sequences in SMC, KG11367.205 (Box 271)
- SA 194-195; SA 197-199, KG11367.206 (Box 271)
  Also identified as: SG VIII.
  Sergei Gaposchkin.
- SA 196, KG11367.207 (Box 271)
  Also identified as: SG VII.
- SA 188-194, KG11367.208 (Box 271)
  Also identified as: SG VI.
- SA 177-182, KG11367.209 (Box 271)
  Also identified as: SG V.
- Star Counts on the LMC, KG11367.210 (Box 272)
- Bright Variable Star Survey, Field 8, KG11367.211 (Box 272)
- Measures of Peruvian Pole Star plates, 1901; KG11367.212 (Box 272)
- VSF Variables SA 16, MW 208, Anticenter 601+17.6, 122, 190, KG11367.213 (Box 272)
  L.R. Ford Layzer.
- VSF Variables NSF 299, 305, 679, 298, KG11367.214 (Box 272)
  A. Hearn and T.K..
  T.K. identity uncertain.
- Positions of Variables around LMC, KG11367.215 (Box 272)
  Margaret Walton Mayall.
- Sequences in LMC, KG11367.216 (Box 272)
- Nebulous Objects in MCs, 1953; KG11367.217 (Box 272)
- AM Plate Milky Way Atlas, KG11367.218 (Box 272)
- Clusters in MCs, KG11367.219 (Box 272)
  Harlow Shapley and Virginia McKibben Nail.
- Milky Way Borders, KG11367.220 (Box 272)
  Harlow Shapley and J. Sweeney.
  Published in Harvard Annals 106#3.
- Positions in omega Cen, KG11367.221 (Box 272)
- O-stars, P-Cyngi stars., KG11367.222 (Box 272)
  Also identified as: A.
  D. Hoffleit.
- Spectra -- eta Car and others., KG11367.223 (Box 272)
  Also identified as: B.
- Spectra., KG11367.224 (Box 272)
  Also identified as: C.
- Spectral Classification - Bright Stars., KG11367.225 (Box 272)
  Also identified as: D.
- Spectral Classification - Bright Stars., KG11367.226 (Box 272)
  Also identified as: E.
- Spectral Classification - Bright Stars., KG11367.227 (Box 272)
  Also identified as: F.
- Spectral Classification - Bright Stars., KG11367.228 (Box 272)
  Also identified as: G.
- Spectral Classification - Bright Stars., KG11367.229 (Box 272)
  Also identified as: H.
- Spectral Classification - Bright Stars., KG11367.230 (Box 272)
- Spectral Classification - Bright Stars., KG11367.231
  Also identified as: J.
- Spectral Classification - Bright Stars., KG11367.232
  Also identified as: K.
- Spectral Classification - Bright Stars., KG11367.233
  Also identified as: L.
- Miscellaneous., KG11367.234
  Also identified as: M.